let's look at the answer to our fault
classification quiz
the phone got wet
by cause
it's definitely an environmental fault
what kind of fault by duration is it
getting wet is a transient fault
eventually it gets dry the explosion
would have been a permanent fault from
which you cannot really recover but
getting wet is only a transient fault
now because the phone was supposed to
prevent itself from running when wet the
fact that it did heat up and it wasn't
supposed to is a indication of a design
fault
so really it was supposed to not do this
but the way it was designed actually
made it do that so it's a design fault
and design faults are typically
permanent and this is one more example
of when you can have a fault
that never becomes an error or a failure
so
the permanent fault of being poorly
designed so that when it gets wet it can
heat up and explode
would never become an error or a failure
until we actually get that particular
phone wet